In this lesson we've talked about order things in sequence.
在本课中，我们讨论了按顺序排列事物。
We've talked about dates we've talked about symbols.
我们讨论了日期，我们讨论了符号。
Now let's talk about numbers.
现在让我们谈谈数字。
Now I know this lesson might be not as interesting a little little boring compared to the other lessons
现在我知道与其他课程相比，这节课可能没有那么有趣有点无聊
but it's very important basic stuff.
但这是非常重要的基本内容。
Let's go through basically how we can say numbers will move pretty quickly so that it's not too hopefully
让我们基本上看一下我们如何说数字会很快移动，这样就不会太有希望了
not too dry.
不要太干。
One very very important thing to remember when it comes to numbers is all you have to do to say numbers
谈到数字时要记住的一件非常重要的事情就是你只需要说出数字
clearly is group them in threes not including this decimal but the group them in threes and within each
显然是将它们分成三组，不包括这个小数，而是将它们分成三组并在每个组内
group of three between commas you just say the number.
逗号之间的三个组，您只需说出数字即可。
So this would be I think you can probably guess one hundred and seven.
所以这就是我想你可能会猜到一百零七。
This would be three hundred and forty nine and the best way to know how to say a very big number is
这将是三百四十九，知道如何说出一个非常大的数字的最好方法是
to count commas.
数逗号。
That's really all you have to do.
这就是你所要做的。
You need to know how to say the number between zero and nine hundred ninety nine.
你需要知道如何说出零到九百九十九之间的数字。
OK.
好的。
And you need to know how to count commas and you need to know what each of these commas means or what
你需要知道如何计算逗号，你需要知道每个逗号的含义或什么
each of them represents.
他们每个人都代表。
This is thousand the first comma is thousand.
这是千，第一个逗号是千。
The second one is million.
第二个是百万。
The third one is billion.
第三个是十亿。
And if you really want to know the next one is trillion but you don't often need to say that.
如果你真的想知道下一个是万亿，但你通常不需要这么说。
OK.
好的。
So a thousand million billion if there are three commas you're going to say billion then million then
所以一千亿如果有三个逗号你会说十亿然后百万然后
thousand.
千。
If there are two commas you're going to say million and then thousand.
如果有两个逗号，你会说百万，然后是千。
If there is only one comma then you're just going to say thousand.
如果只有一个逗号，那么你只会说千。
OK.
好的。
That's all you need to know if there are no commas then you don't need to say any of them and you just
如果没有逗号，这就是您需要知道的所有内容，那么您无需说出任何逗号，您只需
say either.
说要么。
Hundred or if it doesn't have one hundred then we don't even need to talk about that because you already
一百，或者如果没有一百，那我们甚至不需要谈论那个，因为你已经
know.
知道。
OK.
好的。
Count commas.
数逗号。
The other thing you need to know is this.
你需要知道的另一件事是这个。
You do not need to add and between every number that makes it much more complicated.
您不需要在每个数字之间添加和，这会使它变得更加复杂。
You don't need to do that.
你不需要这样做。
You usually only need to use and if there is a zero in front of the last number in front of the very
您通常只需要使用 and 如果在非常前面的最后一个数字前面有一个零
end of the number.
号码的结尾。
That's the only time you usually need to use an OK.
这是您通常需要使用 OK 的唯一时间。
So for example this might be one hundred seven.
例如，这可能是一百七。
You don't have to say and but you could say one hundred and seven one hundred and seven.
你不必说，但你可以说一百零七一百零七。
This might be one thousand and seven in fact you should probably say one thousand and seven.
这可能是一千零七，实际上您可能应该说一千零七。
If you say one thousand seven it's OK it's OK but that's when you would usually use and otherwise don't
如果你说一千七，没关系，没关系，但那是你通常会使用的时候，否则不要
do it.
做。
It just makes it harder and you have more to think about.
它只会让事情变得更难，你需要考虑更多。
OK.
好的。
The last thing that you need to know is after this show we say dot point.
你需要知道的最后一件事是在这个节目之后我们说点点。
Period after this point O P O I N T.
在此之后的时期 O P O I N T。
And we say point point after that.
然后我们说点点。
Just say the number.
只说号码。
You don't need to think about hundreds thousands millions or anything just say the number directly.
您无需考虑数十亿或任何事情，只需直接说出数字即可。
So let's go through these.
所以让我们来看看这些。
OK.
好的。
This one one hundred and seven one hundred and seven.
这一百零七一百零七。
This one one hundred seventy one hundred seventy.
这一百七十七百七十。
Next one one thousand and seven one thousand and seven.
接下来一一千零七一千零七。
OK one thousand seventy one thousand seventy.
好一千七万一七十。
You can say one thousand and seventy if you want to.
如果你愿意，你可以说一千七十。
You don't have to.
你不必。
OK.
好的。
This one one thousand seven hundred one thousand seven hundred one thousand seven hundred and one one
这一千七十一千七十一千七百零一
thousand seven hundred and one.
一千七百零一。
OK.
好的。
Let's get a little bigger.
让我们变得更大一点。
Seventeen thousand.
一万七千。
Because there's one comma.
因为只有一个逗号。
Seventeen thousand five hundred eighty seven.
一万七千五百八十七。
Don't need to use end at all.
根本不需要使用 end 。
Then we can say it more quickly seventeen thousand five hundred eighty seven.
那么我们可以更快地说一万七千五百八十七。
Seventeen thousand five hundred eighty seven.
一万七千五百八十七。
You have to be able to say numbers very quickly.
你必须能够很快说出数字。
Seventeen thousand five hundred eighty seven should be very natural.
一万七千五百八十七应该是很自然的。
Very easy immediate.
非常容易立即。
OK.
好的。
Numbers are getting bigger but it doesn't get harder.
数字越来越大，但并没有变得更难。
One hundred seven thousand one hundred and seven point 1 0 7 7 0 1.
170107 点 1 0 7 7 0 1。
Easy.
简单的。
1 0 7 7 0 1.
1 0 7 7 0 1。
Can we say 1 0 7 7 0 1.
我们可以说 1 0 7 7 0 1。
Yeah.
是的。
That's OK you can say that 1 0 7 7 0 1.
没关系，你可以说 1 0 7 7 0 1。
No problem.
没问题。
OK.
好的。
Now we have one two three three commas.
现在我们有一个二三三逗号。
So that means we need to say billion.
所以这意味着我们需要说十亿。
Million and thousand.
万千。
OK.
好的。
So let's try this very easy 1 billion one hundred seventy one million one hundred seventy thousand seven
所以让我们试试这个非常简单的 1017117007
hundred and one point one three.
一百零一点一三。
Very easy one billion one hundred seventy one billion one hundred seventy thousand seven hundred and
很容易 1171017070
one point one three.
一分三。
Very simple.
很简单。
OK last one.
好的最后一个。
Well it looks so long so scary but it's actually not it's actually not.
好吧，它看起来那么长那么可怕，但实际上并非如此。
I realized that I've killed all the comments.
我意识到我已经杀死了所有的评论。
But I can read it without.
但我可以在没有的情况下阅读它。
And I think you can too.
我认为你也可以。
All right three hundred forty nine billion two hundred thirty million four hundred sixty seven thousand
好的三千四千九十亿二亿三千四十六万七千
three hundred and four point seven six five three hundred forty nine billion two hundred thirty million
三百零四点七六五三百四千九二亿三千万
four hundred sixty seven thousand three hundred and four point seventy six five practice that until
四十六万七千三百零四点七十六五练那直到
it's really easy go online just read an article and find some numbers big numbers small numbers and
上网真的很容易，只需阅读一篇文章并找到一些数字大数字小数字和
just practice saying them again and again follow the simple rules that we just talked about remember
只是练习一遍又一遍地说出它们遵循我们刚刚讨论过的简单规则记住
how many commas you see is the words that you need to say this this or this.
你看到多少个逗号是你需要说这个或这个的词。
Remember that after the decimal you don't need to think about hundreds or thousands.
请记住，小数点后您无需考虑数百或数千。
And remember that usually we don't use and unless there is a zero in front of the last number.
请记住，通常我们不使用and，除非最后一个数字前面有一个零。
And if you remember those things you don't need to know anything else.
如果你记住了这些事情，你就不需要知道其他任何事情。
The most important thing is that you get fast at this when it comes to numbers you shouldn't have to
最重要的是，当涉及到你不应该做的数字时，你会很快
think for a long time about just how to say the number.
想了半天，到底该怎么说这个数字。
It should be automatic.
它应该是自动的。
Should come out of your mouth completely naturally.
应该完全自然地从嘴里出来。 好的。
All right.
所以希望这相对容易。
Practice it until it's really smooth and you can speak and say numbers without thinking.
练习它，直到它真的很流畅，你可以不假思索地说话和说出数字。
Now we're going to quickly go on and talk about math.
现在我们将快速继续讨论数学。